<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-01-23T02:21:04+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Brain Beats Blog | Brainwave Entrainment</title><entry><title type="html">Adrenal Stimulant Rife 3D Frequencies</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/11/adrenal-stimulant-rife-3d-frequencies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adrenal Stimulant Rife 3D Frequencies" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/11/adrenal-stimulant-rife-3d-frequencies</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/11/adrenal-stimulant-rife-3d-frequencies.html">&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a type of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to stimulate the body’s natural healing processes. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, who discovered that certain frequencies could destroy harmful microorganisms and restore health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the benefits of Rife 3D frequencies is that they can help stimulate the adrenal glands, which are responsible for producing hormones that regulate stress, energy, metabolism, and immunity. The adrenal glands can become exhausted or imbalanced due to chronic stress, illness, or environmental toxins, leading to symptoms such as fatigue, anxiety, depression, weight gain, and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use Rife 3D frequencies for adrenal stimulant, you will need a device that can generate and play the frequencies, such as a Rife machine, a frequency generator, or a smartphone app. You will also need headphones or speakers to listen to the frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The frequencies for adrenal stimulant are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10 hz: This frequency helps to balance the brain waves and induce a state of relaxation and calmness. It also stimulates the production of serotonin, a neurotransmitter that regulates mood, sleep, and appetite.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;20 hz: This frequency helps to increase energy and alertness. It also stimulates the production of beta-endorphin, a natural painkiller and mood enhancer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2250 hz: This frequency helps to stimulate the adrenal glands and boost their function. It also helps to detoxify the body and improve blood circulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use these frequencies, you can follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set up your device and headphones or speakers in a comfortable and quiet place.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose the preset and play it for 15 minutes. You can adjust the volume to your preference, but make sure it is not too loud or too soft.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After 15 minutes, stop for few minutes and then play again.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat this process until you have played atleast three times.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can do this once or twice a day, depending on your needs and preferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a safe and natural way to stimulate your adrenal glands and improve your health and well-being. However, they are not a substitute for proper medical care and diagnosis. If you have any health concerns or questions, please consult your doctor before using Rife 3D frequencies or any other alternative therapies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rife 3D frequencies are a type of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to stimulate the body’s natural healing processes. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, who discovered that certain frequencies could destroy harmful microorganisms and restore health.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adnexitis</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/10/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adnexitis.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adnexitis" /><published>2023-04-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/10/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adnexitis</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/10/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adnexitis.html">&lt;p&gt;Adnexitis is a condition that causes inflammation and pain in the ovaries or Fallopian tubes. It can be caused by infections, endometriosis, tumors, or other factors. Adnexitis can affect fertility and increase the risk of complications such as ectopic pregnancy or pelvic abscess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a form of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to target and destroy harmful microorganisms, such as bacteria, viruses, fungi, or parasites. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, who discovered that each microorganism has a resonant frequency that can be used to destroy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I will show you how to use Rife 3D frequencies for adnexitis, using a preset that I have created based on research and experience. This preset contains six frequencies that are designed to eliminate the common causes of adnexitis, such as chlamydia, gonorrhea, mycoplasma, streptococcus, staphylococcus, and candida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;disclaimer&quot;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Rife 3D frequencies are not approved by the FDA or any other regulatory agency and have not been proven to be effective or safe for any condition. You should consult your doctor before using Rife 3D frequencies or any other alternative therapy. You should also follow your doctor’s instructions regarding diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of adnexitis. I am not responsible for any harm or damage that may result from using Rife 3D frequencies or this preset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-use-the-preset&quot;&gt;How to Use the Preset&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, you will need a device that can generate and play Rife 3D frequencies, such as a Spooky2 generator or a smartphone app or website such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://brain-beats.in&quot;&gt;brain beats&lt;/a&gt;. You will also need a way to deliver the frequencies to your body, such as headphones, speakers, contact electrodes, plasma tube, or scalar field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The preset contains six frequencies that are played in sequence for three minutes each. The total duration of the preset is 18 minutes. You can repeat the preset as often as you like, depending on your condition and response. Some people may notice improvement after one session, while others may need several sessions over days or weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The frequencies in this preset are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;440 hz: This frequency is used to balance the body and mind and to enhance the immune system.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;441 hz: This frequency is used to target chlamydia, which is a common cause of adnexitis and can lead to pelvic inflammatory disease (PID) if left untreated.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;522 hz: This frequency is used to target gonorrhea, which is another common cause of adnexitis and PID. Gonorrhea can also cause infertility and increase the risk of HIV transmission.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;572 hz: This frequency is used to target mycoplasma, which is a type of bacteria that can cause adnexitis and PID. Mycoplasma can also cause chronic pelvic pain and urinary tract infections.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3343 hz: This frequency is used to target streptococcus, which is a group of bacteria that can cause adnexitis and PID. Streptococcus can also cause pharyngitis, tonsillitis, scarlet fever, rheumatic fever, and necrotizing fasciitis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3833 hz: This frequency is used to target staphylococcus, which is another group of bacteria that can cause adnexitis and PID. Staphylococcus can also cause skin infections, abscesses, boils, impetigo, cellulitis, and toxic shock syndrome.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5312 hz: This frequency is used to target candida, which is a type of fungus that can cause adnexitis and PID. Candida can also cause vaginal yeast infections, oral thrush, diaper rash, and systemic candidiasis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use the preset, follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Connect your device to your delivery method of choice (headphones, speakers, electrodes, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Load the preset on your device or app&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start the preset and relax&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Listen to the frequencies for 18 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stop the preset and disconnect your device&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drink plenty of water and rest&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a potential alternative therapy for adnexitis that uses sound waves to kill harmful microorganisms. This blog post has shown you how to use a preset that I have created for adnexitis that contains six frequencies that target the common causes of this condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, remember that Rife 3D frequencies are not a substitute for medical care and that you should always consult your doctor before using them or any other alternative therapy. You should also follow your doctor’s advice regarding diagnosis, treatment, and prevention of adnexitis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you found this blog post helpful and informative. If you have any questions, comments, or feedback, please feel free to leave them below. Thank you for reading and stay healthy!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adnexitis is a condition that causes inflammation and pain in the ovaries or Fallopian tubes. It can be caused by infections, endometriosis, tumors, or other factors. Adnexitis can affect fertility and increase the risk of complications such as ectopic pregnancy or pelvic abscess.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adhesions</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/09/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adhesions.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adhesions" /><published>2023-04-09T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-09T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/09/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adhesions</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/09/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adhesions.html">&lt;p&gt;Adhesions are bands of scar tissue that form between organs and tissues, causing pain, inflammation, and reduced mobility. They can result from surgery, infection, trauma, or inflammation. Adhesions can affect any part of the body, but they are most common in the abdomen, pelvis, and chest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the possible ways to treat adhesions is to use Rife 3D frequencies. Rife 3D frequencies are sound waves that are modulated in three dimensions to create a holographic effect. They are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, who discovered that certain frequencies can destroy harmful microorganisms and stimulate healing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are different from traditional Rife frequencies, which are usually single tones or simple waveforms. Rife 3D frequencies are complex and dynamic, creating a more immersive and effective experience. They can also target multiple issues at once, as each frequency has multiple harmonics and subharmonics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use Rife 3D frequencies for adhesions, you will need a device that can generate and play them. There are several options available on the market, such as the Spooky2 Rife Machine, the GB4000 Frequency Generator, the F-Scan Frequency Synthesizer or &lt;a href=&quot;https://brain-beats.in&quot;&gt;brain beats&lt;/a&gt;. You will also need a pair of headphones or speakers to listen to the frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following is a sample healing preset for adhesions using Rife 3D frequencies. You can adjust the duration, intensity, and volume according to your preference and tolerance. You can also add or remove frequencies as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;2720 hz - This frequency helps to dissolve scar tissue and adhesions, as well as to reduce inflammation and pain.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;2170 hz - This frequency helps to improve blood circulation and oxygen delivery to the affected areas, as well as to stimulate cellular regeneration and repair.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;1550 hz - This frequency helps to balance the immune system and fight off infections that may cause or worsen adhesions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;802 hz - This frequency helps to relax the muscles and nerves around the adhesions, as well as to relieve spasms and cramps.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;880 hz - This frequency helps to enhance the healing process and promote tissue growth and regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;787 hz - This frequency helps to boost the overall health and vitality of the body, as well as to support the organs and systems affected by adhesions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;776 hz - This frequency helps to cleanse and detoxify the body from toxins and waste products that may contribute to adhesions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;760 hz - This frequency helps to reduce stress and anxiety that may aggravate adhesions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;727 hz - This frequency helps to eliminate bacteria, viruses, fungi, and parasites that may cause or worsen adhesions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;660 hz - This frequency helps to harmonize the energy flow and balance the chakras in the body, as well as to enhance mental clarity and focus.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;190 hz - This frequency helps to ground and center the body and mind, as well as to calm the emotions and release negative feelings.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, simply play it on your device for at least 15 minutes a day, preferably before bedtime. You can also listen to it while meditating, doing yoga, or performing other relaxing activities. You should notice some improvement in your symptoms within a few weeks of consistent use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Please consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices for your health condition. Rife 3D frequencies are not approved by the FDA or any other regulatory agency. Use them at your own risk and discretion.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adhesions are bands of scar tissue that form between organs and tissues, causing pain, inflammation, and reduced mobility. They can result from surgery, infection, trauma, or inflammation. Adhesions can affect any part of the body, but they are most common in the abdomen, pelvis, and chest.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenovirus HC</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/08/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus-hc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenovirus HC" /><published>2023-04-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/08/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus-hc</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/08/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus-hc.html">&lt;p&gt;Adenovirus HC is a common viral infection that causes respiratory symptoms such as cough, sore throat, fever, and runny nose. It can also affect the eyes, causing conjunctivitis or pink eye. Adenovirus HC is usually mild and self-limiting, but it can sometimes lead to complications such as pneumonia, bronchitis, or ear infections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the alternative therapies that some people use to treat adenovirus HC is Rife 3D frequencies. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the idea that every microorganism has a specific frequency that can be used to destroy it. By exposing the virus to its resonant frequency, it is supposed to rupture and die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are generated by a device that uses three-dimensional sound waves to create a complex frequency spectrum. The device can be connected to a computer or a smartphone and controlled by a software that allows the user to select the desired frequencies and duration of the treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use Rife 3D frequencies for adenovirus HC, you will need a Rife 3D device, a pair of headphones or speakers, and a healing preset that contains the frequencies specific for adenovirus HC. You can find the preset online or create your own using the software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The healing preset for adenovirus HC consists of the following frequencies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;28729.05 hz, 16628.88 hz, 18471.00 hz, 18670.15 hz, 19566.32 hz, 1407.93 hz, 827.90 hz, 919.62 hz, 929.53 hz, 974.15 hz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use the preset, you will need to load it into the software and connect the device to your computer or smartphone. Then, you will need to put on your headphones or place the speakers near your ears. Make sure the volume is comfortable and not too loud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The treatment duration may vary depending on your preference and condition, but a typical session lasts for about 15 minutes. You can repeat the session once or twice a day until your symptoms improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits that users report from using Rife 3D frequencies for adenovirus HC are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reduced inflammation and pain in the throat and chest&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved breathing and oxygenation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enhanced immune system and resistance to infection&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Faster recovery and healing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there is no scientific evidence that Rife 3D frequencies are effective or safe for treating adenovirus HC or any other disease. There are also potential risks and side effects associated with using Rife 3D frequencies, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hearing damage or loss from exposure to high-intensity sound waves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Interference with pacemakers, implants, or other medical devices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Aggravation of existing medical conditions or allergies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unknown long-term effects on the body and brain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, it is important to use Rife 3D frequencies with caution and under the supervision of a qualified health professional. Do not use Rife 3D frequencies as a substitute for conventional medical treatment or without consulting your doctor first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adenovirus HC is a common viral infection that causes respiratory symptoms such as cough, sore throat, fever, and runny nose. It can also affect the eyes, causing conjunctivitis or pink eye. Adenovirus HC is usually mild and self-limiting, but it can sometimes lead to complications such as pneumonia, bronchitis, or ear infections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies to Heal Adenovirus Comp</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/07/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-comp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies to Heal Adenovirus Comp" /><published>2023-04-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/07/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-comp</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/07/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-comp.html">&lt;p&gt;Adenovirus comp is a term used to describe a complex of adenoviruses, which are a group of viruses that can cause respiratory, gastrointestinal, and eye infections. Adenoviruses are very common and can affect anyone, but they are more likely to cause serious illness in people with weakened immune systems, such as children, elderly, or transplant recipients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the alternative ways to treat adenovirus comp is to use Rife 3D frequencies, which are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, an American inventor who claimed to have discovered a way to destroy harmful microorganisms using sound waves. Rife 3D frequencies are generated by a device that emits soundwave pulses at specific frequencies that are supposed to resonate with and destroy the target pathogens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I will show you how to use Rife 3D frequencies to heal adenovirus comp using a preset that I have created. This preset contains 40 frequencies that are based on the research of various Rife practitioners and enthusiasts. The frequencies in this preset are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10000 hz, 7767 hz, 7762 hz, 7702 hz, 7009 hz, 7001 hz, 6989 hz, 5000 hz, 4868 hz, 2720 hz, 2050 hz, 1500 hz, 1395 hz, 1062 hz, 1060 hz, 1034 hz, 1009 hz, 969 hz, 968 hz, 962 hz, 959 hz, 960 hz, 952 hz, 951 hz, 942 hz, 880 hz, 1550 hz, 802 hz, 787 hz, 768 hz, 728 hz, 690 hz, 660 hz, 555 hz, 523 hz, 522 hz, 1865 hz, 444 hz, 333 hz, 300 hz, 180 hz, 160 hz, 125 hz, 95 hz, 72 hz, 60 hz, 48 hz, 26 hz, 20 hz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, you will need a Rife software that can generate these frequencies and deliver them to your body. There are many types of Rife software available on the market. You will also need a software program that can control the device and run the preset. I recommend using  &lt;a href=&quot;https://brain-beats.in&quot;&gt;brain beats website&lt;/a&gt;, which is free and compatible with most most speakers and headphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To run the preset, follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Connect your Rife device to your computer and launch brain beats software.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to the 3D rife frequency section and search the name “adenovirus comp”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on play button on the preset.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adjust the volume of the sound.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You could use headphones or directly speakers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The preset will run indefinately. You can adjust the intensity of the frequencies according to your preference and tolerance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat the treatment once or twice a day until you feel better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some tips for using Rife frequencies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drink plenty of water before and after the treatment to flush out toxins.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Eat healthy foods and avoid sugar and processed foods that can feed the viruses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take supplements that can boost your immune system and support your organs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rest well and avoid stress as much as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monitor your symptoms and consult your doctor if they worsen or persist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this blog post was helpful and informative. Please share your feedback and results in the comments section below. Remember that Rife frequencies are not a substitute for medical care and that you should always consult your doctor before trying any alternative therapies. Stay healthy and happy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This is not medical advice and should not be taken as such. The information in this blog post is for educational and entertainment purposes only. The author is not a licensed physician and does not endorse or recommend any of the products or methods mentioned here. Use them at your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adenovirus comp is a term used to describe a complex of adenoviruses, which are a group of viruses that can cause respiratory, gastrointestinal, and eye infections. Adenoviruses are very common and can affect anyone, but they are more likely to cause serious illness in people with weakened immune systems, such as children, elderly, or transplant recipients.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies to Heal Adenovirus 36 Infection</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/06/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-36-infection.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies to Heal Adenovirus 36 Infection" /><published>2023-04-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/06/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-36-infection</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/06/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-to-heal-adenovirus-36-infection.html">&lt;p&gt;Adenovirus 36 (AD-36) is a type of virus that can cause respiratory infections, conjunctivitis, and gastroenteritis. Some studies have also suggested that AD-36 may be related to weight gain in some people, as it can affect the metabolism and fat storage of cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a form of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to target and destroy pathogens, such as viruses, bacteria, fungi, and parasites. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the work of Dr. Royal Raymond Rife, who discovered that each microorganism has a unique frequency that can be used to kill it without harming the surrounding healthy tissue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I will show you how to use Rife 3D frequencies to heal AD-36 infection and possibly reduce its effects on your weight. You will need a device that can generate Rife 3D frequencies, such as a Spooky2 generator or a Brain Beats. You will also need a pair of headphones or speakers to listen to the frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The frequencies that I will use in this preset are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;8875 hz: This is the main frequency for AD-36, according to the Consolidated Annotated Frequency List (CAFL).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;6140 hz: This is a secondary frequency for AD-36, also from the CAFL.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5859 hz: This is a frequency for weight loss, according to the Spooky2 database.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5797 hz: This is another frequency for weight loss, also from the Spooky2 database.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5219 hz: This is a frequency for fat metabolism, according to the Spooky2 database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Connect your device to your computer and load the preset file. You can play the preset file from this website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://brain-beats.in&quot;&gt;brain beats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plug in your headphones or speakers and adjust the volume to a comfortable level. You should be able to hear the frequencies clearly, but not too loud.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start the program and listen to the frequencies for at least 30 minutes per day. You can listen longer if you wish, but do not exceed 2 hours per day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat this process daily until your symptoms improve or disappear. You may also notice changes in your weight or body fat percentage over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: This preset is not a substitute for proper medical diagnosis and treatment. If you have any serious or chronic health conditions, please consult your doctor before using Rife 3D frequencies. Some people may experience side effects such as headache, nausea, fatigue, or detoxification symptoms when using Rife 3D frequencies. If this happens, stop the program and drink plenty of water. Resume the program when you feel better or lower the volume or duration of the sessions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This is not medical advice and should not be taken as such. Consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adenovirus 36 (AD-36) is a type of virus that can cause respiratory infections, conjunctivitis, and gastroenteritis. Some studies have also suggested that AD-36 may be related to weight gain in some people, as it can affect the metabolism and fat storage of cells.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenovirus</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/05/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenovirus" /><published>2023-04-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/05/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/05/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenovirus.html">&lt;p&gt;Adenovirus is a common virus that can cause various infections, such as colds, flu, bronchitis, pneumonia, gastroenteritis, and conjunctivitis. It can affect anyone, but it is more likely to cause serious complications in people with weakened immune systems, such as children, elderly, and transplant recipients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no specific treatments or vaccines for adenovirus infections, so the best way to prevent them is to practice good hygiene, avoid contact with sick people, and boost your immune system. However, if you do get infected, there is a natural and alternative way to help your body fight off the virus: Rife 3D frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are sound waves that are designed to resonate with the frequency of a specific pathogen, such as a virus, bacteria, fungus, or parasite. By exposing the pathogen to its resonant frequency, you can disrupt its structure and function, and eventually destroy it. This is based on the principle of sympathetic resonance, which states that when two objects have the same natural frequency, they will vibrate in harmony when one of them is stimulated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are different from the original Rife frequencies, which were invented by Dr. Royal Raymond Rife in the 1930s. Rife 3D frequencies use three-dimensional sound waves that can penetrate deeper into the body and reach the hidden places where pathogens may hide. Rife 3D frequencies also use a wider range of frequencies that can target multiple strains of a pathogen at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use Rife 3D frequencies for adenovirus, you will need a device that can generate and play these frequencies, such as a smartphone, tablet, computer, or speaker. You will also need a healing preset that contains the specific frequencies for adenovirus. A healing preset is a file that contains a sequence of frequencies that are played for a certain duration and interval. You can download or create your own healing presets using various apps or software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One example of a healing preset for adenovirus is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;333 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;523 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;666 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;786 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;768 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;959 hz&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;962 hz&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, you will need to wrap it in codeblock syntax (triple backticks) like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, you will need to play it using your device at a comfortable volume level. You can listen to it with or without headphones, depending on your preference. You should listen to it at least once a day until your symptoms improve or disappear. You can also combine it with other natural remedies, such as herbal teas, honey, garlic, ginger, vitamin C, and zinc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Rife 3D frequencies are not approved by the FDA or any other regulatory agency and have not been scientifically proven to treat or cure any disease. You should consult your doctor before using Rife 3D frequencies or any other alternative therapy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adenovirus is a common virus that can cause various infections, such as colds, flu, bronchitis, pneumonia, gastroenteritis, and conjunctivitis. It can affect anyone, but it is more likely to cause serious complications in people with weakened immune systems, such as children, elderly, and transplant recipients.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenoma Cervical</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/04/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenoma-cervical.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Adenoma Cervical" /><published>2023-04-04T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-04T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/04/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenoma-cervical</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/04/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-adenoma-cervical.html">&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are a type of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to target different health conditions. They are based on the work of Dr. Royal Rife, who claimed to have discovered the resonant frequencies of various pathogens and diseases in the 1930s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the conditions that Rife 3D frequencies can help with is adenoma cervical, which is a type of epithelial tumor of the cervix that can be either benign or malignant. Adenoma cervical is also known as cervical cancer, and it is one of the most common cancers among women worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Rife 3D frequencies theory, adenoma cervical has a resonant frequency of 433 hz, which means that exposing the tumor to this frequency can cause it to vibrate and break down. This can reduce the size and growth of the tumor, and potentially eliminate it completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use Rife 3D frequencies for adenoma cervical, you will need a device that can generate and emit sound waves at 433 hz. You can use a smartphone app, a computer program, or a dedicated Rife machine. You will also need a pair of headphones or speakers to listen to the frequency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recommended protocol for using Rife 3D frequencies for adenoma cervical is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set your device to play the frequency of 433 hz continuously or in pulses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place your headphones over your ears or your speakers near your cervix.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Listen to the frequency for at least 15 minutes, twice a day, for six weeks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monitor your symptoms and consult your doctor regularly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people may experience side effects from using Rife 3D frequencies, such as headaches, nausea, fatigue, or dizziness. These are usually mild and temporary, and can be reduced by drinking plenty of water and resting between sessions. However, if you experience any severe or persistent side effects, stop using the frequency and seek medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are not a substitute for conventional medical treatment, and they should not be used without consulting your doctor. They are not approved by the FDA or any other regulatory agency, and their effectiveness and safety have not been proven by scientific studies. Use them at your own risk and discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This is not medical advice and should not be taken as such. Consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rife 3D frequencies are a type of sound therapy that uses specific frequencies to target different health conditions. They are based on the work of Dr. Royal Rife, who claimed to have discovered the resonant frequencies of various pathogens and diseases in the 1930s.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Adenoids Rife 3D frequencies</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/03/adenoids-rife-3d-frequencies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adenoids Rife 3D frequencies" /><published>2023-04-03T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/03/adenoids-rife-3d-frequencies</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/03/adenoids-rife-3d-frequencies.html">&lt;p&gt;Adenoids are small glands that are located at the back of the nose. They are part of the immune system and help fight infections. However, sometimes they can become enlarged or infected, causing symptoms such as nasal congestion, snoring, ear infections, or difficulty breathing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people claim that Rife 3D frequencies can help shrink or eliminate adenoids by using sound waves to destroy harmful microorganisms. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the idea that every living thing has a specific frequency, and that applying a matching frequency can cause resonance and destroy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I will share with you a Rife 3D frequencies healing preset for adenoids that I found online. The preset consists of 26 frequencies that are supposed to target the adenoids and the bacteria or viruses that cause inflammation. The frequencies are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1550 hz, 802 hz, 880 hz, 787 hz, 776 hz, 727 hz, 444 hz, 20 hz, 428 hz, 660 hz, 2720 hz, 2170 hz, 14 hz, 333 hz, 523 hz, 768 hz, 786 hz, 428 hz, 1865 hz, 590 hz, 690 hz, 780 hz, 807 hz, 810 hz, 1570 hz, 2000 hz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, you will need a device that can generate and play these frequencies. You can use a computer software, a smartphone app, or a dedicated Rife machine. You will also need a pair of headphones or speakers to listen to the frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recommended duration for this preset is 30 minutes per day for at least two weeks. You should listen to the frequencies at a comfortable volume level and relax while doing so. You can also combine this preset with other treatments or remedies that your doctor prescribes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this blog post was helpful and informative. Please remember that Rife 3D frequencies are not a substitute for professional medical care and that you should always consult your doctor before trying any new therapy. Thank you for reading and stay healthy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Rife 3D frequencies are not proven to be effective or safe for any condition. Consult your doctor before using any alternative or complementary therapy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Adenoids are small glands that are located at the back of the nose. They are part of the immune system and help fight infections. However, sometimes they can become enlarged or infected, causing symptoms such as nasal congestion, snoring, ear infections, or difficulty breathing.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Acute Pain Relief</title><link href="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/02/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-pain-relief.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Use Rife 3D Frequencies for Acute Pain Relief" /><published>2023-04-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/02/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-pain-relief</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://brain-beats.in/blog/blog/2023/04/02/how-to-use-rife-3d-frequencies-for-pain-relief.html">&lt;p&gt;Acute pain is a type of pain that lasts for a short time and usually has a clear cause, such as an injury, infection, or surgery. Acute pain can be mild, moderate, or severe, and it can affect any part of the body. Acute pain can interfere with your daily activities and quality of life, so finding effective ways to manage it is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the methods that some people use to cope with acute pain is Rife 3D frequencies. Rife 3D frequencies are based on the idea that certain frequencies of sound can affect the cells and tissues of the body, and that by applying specific frequencies to the area of pain, you can reduce inflammation, promote healing, and relieve discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are generated by a website called a brain beats, which emits sound waves through speakers attached to the computer or smartphone. The Rife machine can be programmed with different presets that contain a sequence of frequencies for various conditions. One of the presets that is designed for acute pain is called Acute Pain Rife 3D frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The frequencies in this preset are: 3000 hz, 95 hz, 10000 hz, 1550 hz, 802 hz, 880 hz, 787 hz, 727 hz, 690 hz, 666 hz. These frequencies are said to target the nerves, muscles, bones, and immune system involved in acute pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use this preset, you need to have a computer or smartphone that supports Rife 3D frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have the preset on your device, you can follow these steps to use it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Attach the earphones to the computer or smartphone.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Search the Acute Pain Rife 3D frequencies preset and press play.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adjust the intensity of the output according to your comfort level. You should feel a slight tingling sensation but not pain or discomfort.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Run the preset for at least 15 minutes or as long as you need. You can repeat the session up to three times a day or as directed by your doctor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After each session, drink plenty of water to flush out any toxins that may have been released by the frequencies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monitor your pain level and any changes in your condition. If you experience any adverse effects, stop using the Rife machine and consult your doctor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rife 3D frequencies are not a substitute for conventional medical treatment and should be used with caution and under supervision. There is no scientific evidence that Rife 3D frequencies can cure any disease or condition, and they may have unknown risks or interactions with other therapies or medications. Always consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This blog post is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Consult your doctor before using any alternative therapies or devices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Acute pain is a type of pain that lasts for a short time and usually has a clear cause, such as an injury, infection, or surgery. Acute pain can be mild, moderate, or severe, and it can affect any part of the body. Acute pain can interfere with your daily activities and quality of life, so finding effective ways to manage it is important.</summary></entry></feed>